[
    {
        "key":"how",
        "data_list":[
            {
                
                    "question":"how can i give you the orders",
                    "answer":"you can connect to our system first, then our team will contact you and follow your orders daily.\nThis is the step to connect our system\nhttps://mutualdropshipping.com/make-it-connect-our-system/\nAfter connecting the store, we can see your order, and make an invoice for you after we ship, the tracking number can update by automatic In your store.",
                    "arabic_answer":"يمكن أولا الشبك مع نظامنا ، بعد ذلك سيتواصل معك احد موظفينا ، ويتابع طلباتك يومياً."
                },
            {
                    "question":"how long can i get the tracking number and how",
                    "answer":"Our processing time is 1-3 days to buy the goods. After our warehouse is checked the quality then we will ship it. When they scan the order the shipping number will upload to your store automatically.",
                    "arabic_answer": "عادة تستغرق عملية شراء المنتجات من يوم إلى ثلاثة ايام ، بعد ذلك سيقوم عمّالنا في المستودع بتفحص جوده المنتجات ، وعند مسحهم لكود المنتج سيتم رفع رقم التتبع الخاص بمنتجك بشكل تلقائي لمتجرك."
                },
            {
                    "question":"how can i make the payment",
                    "answer":"Please check this link which already includes all payment information.\nhttps://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1y62XdilnMxjZqW51pMxjWCEGwSL8LShp/edit?usp=sharing&ouid=107045962749751827739&rtpof=true&sd=true",
                    "arabic_answer": "جميع معلومات الدفع في الرابط ادناه : \nhttps://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1y62XdilnMxjZqW51pMxjWCEGwSL8LShp/edit?usp=sharing&ouid=107045962749751827739&rtpof=true&sd=true"
                },
            {
                    "question":"how can i place the orders",
                    "answer":"After you connect our system, we will send you the invoice, then you make the payment and we will purchase the goods to ship.",
                    "arabic_answer": "بعدك انتهاءك من عملية الربط مع نظامنا ، سنقوم بارسال الفاتوره لك ، ثم ستقوم بالدفع ، بعد ذلك سنقول بارسال المنتجات للعنوان المطلوب."
                },
            {
                    "question":"how many warehouses do you have",
                    "answer":"China:2 warehouse\nDE:1 warehouse\nUSA:1 warehouse",
                    "arabic_answer":"الصين : مستودعين \n ألمانيا : مستودع واحد \n إمريكا: مستودع واحد"
                }
       ]
    },{
        "key":"why",
        "data_list":[
            {
                    "question":"why haven't you fulfilled the order yet",
                    "answer":"when payment is arranged,we will proceed to buy the goods, it takes about 3 days for goods to arrive, it depends on the distance between the factory and our warehouse, sometimes will fastest, and our warehouse will ship it immediately when goods arrive, we will try our best to proceed things as fast as we can, please be noted, thanks ~\nand if you want us to upload the tracking number to the customer firstly in advance, just please inform us, it is also ok.\n（ps. here is Mutual Dropshipping Process Process, please kindly check, so you will know more about our process, thanks",
                    "arabic_answer": "بعد اتمامك لعملية الدفع ، سنقوم بعملية شراء المنتج ، والذي بدوره يحتاج لثلاث أيام تقريباً، وهذا يعتمد على المسافة بين المصنع والمستودع ، يقوم العمّال بمستودعاتنا ببعث المنتج باقصى وقت ممكن ؛ سنحاول اتمام العملية باسرع وقت ممكن ، شكرا على تفهمك \n في حال اردت أن نرسل رقم التتبع لزبونك بشكل مسبق ، يرجى اخبارنا بذلك."
            }
       ]
    },{
        "key":"which",
        "data_list":[
            {
                    "question":"which country will you ship to",
                    "answer":"we can ship to all countries.",
                    "arabic_answer": "نوفر عملية ارسال المنتجات لجميع دول العالم"
            }
       ]
    },{
        "key":"can",
        "data_list":[
            {
                    "question":"need to pay for every purchase from you so that you can buy from the manufacturer correct",
                    "answer":"yes,In order to avoid delaying your orders, we suggest that you arrange a part of payments as credit in our account, so if you have orders, we can purchase the goods the first time, it will be faster to process your orders, please note, thank you!",
                    "arabic_answer": "نعم ، لتجنب تأخير عملية ارسال طلباتك ، نقترح عليك ايداع مبلغ من المال لحسابنا ، في هذه الحالة عند استلامنا أي من طلباتك سنقوم باقتصاص المبلغ بشكل مباشر وارسال الطلب فوراً."
                
            },
            {
                    "question":"can you send me your winning products",
                    "answer":"You can come to the below links to check it , we will keep updating:\n1.\nWebsite:https://mutualdropshipping.com/\n2.\nIns:https://instagram.com/mutualdropshipping?utm_medium=copy_link\n3.Youtube:https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4EsSDOQJSfXEgcK8djHyNw\n4.Facebook:https://www.facebook.com/DropshippingMutual/",
                    "arabic_answer": "يمكنك تصفح افضل منتجاتنا عن طريق موقعنا الرسمي ، أو أي من حساب من حسابات التواصل الإجتماعي لدينا . \n الموقع الإلكتروني : https://mutualdropshipping.com \n الإنستقرام: https://instagram.com/mutualdropshipping \n قناة اليوتيوب : https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC4EsSDOQJSfXEgcK8djHyNw \n صفحة الفيسبوك : https://www.facebook.com/DropshippingMutual"
            },
            {
                    "question":"can you ship the goods on the same day",
                    "answer":"If you already purchased the stocks in our china warehouse or overseas warehouse, after you make the shipping payment, we can ship it on the same day.",
                    "arabic_answer":"اذا طلبت من عندنا نفس المنتج من قبل ، ودفعت بنفس اليوم ، نعم يمكننا ارسال الطلب بنفس اليوم"
            },
            {
                    "question":"you have a warehouse in germany,can you ship from germany",
                    "answer":"yes, you can ship the products in bulk to our Germany warehouse first, then we can ship from Germany directly.",
                    "arabic_answer": "نعم ، يمكنك شراء المنتج بالجملة وارساله لألمانيا ثم ارسال الطلبات من هناك."
            }
       ]
    },{
        "key":"do",
        "data_list":[
            {
                    "question":"do you inspect the products",
                    "answer":"Yes, we will make the inspection",
                    "arabic_answer": "نعم ، نقوم بفحص جميع المنتجات قبل ارسالها لوجهتها النهائية"
            },
            {
                    "question":"i do not want the transaction number to be added if the order is not yet in the destination country",
                    "answer":"We can do a manual setup for your order without showing domestic logistics. Or directly choose a channel that does not display domestic logistics in China",
                    "arabic_answer": "يمكننا اتمام العملية بشكل يدوي من دون اظهار المعلومات اللوجستية ، أو عن طريق اختيار القناة التي لا تظهر معلومات  العملية اللوجستية في الصين."
            },
            {
                    "question":"do you accept paypal",
                    "answer":"our PayPal is not available now, and we also have Wise Payoneer and Stripe, they are ok.\nplease be noted. \nthanks",
                    "arabic_answer": "لا يوجد لدينا حساب في البيبال  حاليا ، حساباتنا متوفره فقط على wise , payoneer , stripe "
            }
       ]
    },{
        "key":"where",
        "data_list":[
            {
                    "question":"where is your warehouse address,our customer wants a return to china",
                    "answer":"Dear, If the customer wants to return the goods, the customer will bear the return shipping cost. please note it :\nAddress：2nd Floor, No. 35, Tazhou Road, Ta xia zhou, Jiangdong Street, Yiwu City, Zhejiang Province, China\nPost code：322000\nName： Mr.Cao\nPhone number：13955421007",
                    "arabic_answer": "اذا اراد الزبون ارجاع الطلب ، يحتمل الزبون تكاليف الشحن ، معلومات ارجاع الشحنة : \n الموقع : \n 2nd Floor, No. 35, Tazhou Road, Ta xia zhou, Jiangdong Street, Yiwu City, Zhejiang Province, China \n الرمز البريدي : 322000 \n اسم المستلم : Mr.Cao \n رقم الهاتف : 13955421007"
            }
       ]
    },{
        "key":"what",
        "data_list":[
            {
                    "question":"what is your email",
                    "answer":"Our company email is: sales@mutualdropshipping.com",
                    "arabic_answer":"sales@mutualdropshipping.com"
            }
       ]
    }
]
